♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester ♪
♪ And TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an
evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment needed
a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked him
on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him
into space ♪
MIKE: Get me down.
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Now, keep in mind,
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies begin
or end ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep
his sanity ♪
♪ With the help
of his robot friends ♪
Robot roll call.
-Cambot.
-Show yourself.
-Gypsy.
-Oh, hurry!
-Tom Servo.
-Hello there.
-Crow.
-That's one "o".
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
[ Doors closing ]
Ooh, ow, oh, oh.
Oh, hi, everyone. Welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
I'm Mike Nelson.
I'm sorry to say
I have a really--
a really pretty bad headache.
-Ugh.
-Oh, a headache?
-Yeah.
-Oh, well.
That's too bad, Mike.
But I've got to practice
my cymbals.
I got a big
recital tomorrow.
No. No, no.
Crow, could you not...?
Hey, Mike, look what
I found here, a bagpipe.
Any requests?
Well, Servo, I have a headache.
No, I don't know that one?
How about Amazing Grace?
Well...
I just saw Seinfeld.
I love it so much.
[ Laughing ]
No!
Jeez, Mike,
could you keep it down?
Yeah, have some
consideration, jeez.
I like Kramer.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, yeah, that's it.
Ugh, oh,
I'm a miracle worker, baby.
Oh, yeah.
We'll be right back.
Oh, that's better.
[ Music playing ]
[ Machine whirring ]
CROW: Mike, no.
What?
I have to relieve the pressure.
It's the only way.
Oh, well.
At least, wear
your safety glasses.
Oh, you know,
that's a good point.
-Maybe I should.
-Oh, every time I have
-a project-- what?
-Got a headache?
Good.
Look, I'm completely backed up
on experiments this week,
so I've sent you up
a little chemistry set.
Invent something,
do the paperwork
and send it down to me, okay?
Oh, and falsify some lab reports
while you're at it.
Oh, chop-chop.
Let's see what my little Frank
is up to, shall we?
Oh, you know, cloning.
Just recombining some DNA
that I found in this chunky
little piece of amber.
Oh, like that's hard.
Oh.
Well, hey, there.
Hi, I'm Frank.
What's your name?
Frank, this is fascinating.
I think it was my turning
the Bunsen burner up
that did the trick.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, jeez.
[ Grunting ]
No.
Bad.
No, no.
He'll be oblivious
like Mike, okay...
No.
Hey, cool.
Chemistry sets.
I know.
Doo, doo, doo, doo, doo.
Maraschino cherry.
Servo, drink this.
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
[ Gulping ]
Hmm, kind of a minty sort of...
I thought it was...
[ Coughing ]
[ Indistinct ]
No.
-Whoa.
Servo, what have we done?
Servo, is that you?
-Servo kill?
-No.
-You don't like Servo?
-What did I do?
No, no, no, we like Servo.
It's just that Servo no kill.
-No.
-Oh, don't touch Servo.
No, touch bad.
No touch Servo.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Servo hungry.
We'll get you a cookie.
Servo no like cookie.
-What a baby.
-Shh, no, shh.
Dr. Forrester, help.
He's so cute
when he's sleeping, Frank.
Yes, he is.
I think he's used to me now.
And I don't think
we have anything
to worry about.
Well, your movie this week
is a real treat.
Ow, jeez.
Oh, jeez.
No, bad.
It's called
"High School Big Shot".
And-- oh.
That is not nice.
Bad.
There's another bag of these.
-Oh, we got-- movie sign.
-CROW: Movie sign.
SERVO: Servo kill movie sign.
[ Doors opening ]
[ Indistinct chatter ]
CROW: Hey, he treed her.
Is the devil
wearing satin tap pants?
NARRATOR: There are those
who would say that the story
which follows could happen
only in a dream.
-SERVO: Movie bad.
-MIKE: Yes.
NARRATOR: Regardless of where
it could happen,
this is the way it did happen.
-SERVO: Movie, go away.
-NARRATOR: The story involves
Bill Dudley, a mighty darn good
wholesale bakery salesman.
-MIKE: And that's about it.
-NARRATOR: A character
named Red,
who actually is nothing
more than a file clerk.
-CROW: Huh?
-NARRATOR: And one named
Whitey, who
is similarly employed,
- so to speak.
-CROW: Hey, Whitey.
NARRATOR: It all starts
in this rather strange
and out of this world office.
Which keeps the sales records
of every wholesale
- bakery salesman on earth.
- CROW: Mm-hmm.
NARRATOR: Or so the story goes.
MIKE: Well, it's your story.
NARRATOR: Whitey is entrusted
with the records
- of good salesman.
-SERVO: Hate movie.
NARRATOR: Red?
The other kind.
CROW: The fugitive kind.
NARRATOR: Now,
it seems that Red and Whitey
never see eye to eye on them.
-SERVO: [ Grunting ]
-MIKE: What are you doing?
NARRATOR: This leads to many
arguments
...in the midst of them.
-CROW: Oh.
-MIKE: Whoa.
Must you beat
on that confounded thing
-all the time?
-MIKE: You okay?
SERVO: Yeah.
I guess it kind of wore off.
-I am not beating.
-MIKE: Weird, weird.
I'm playing.
Well, whatever it is,
it sounds awful.
You're just peeved
because another bread group
salesman has been transferred
from your record to mine.
-Bill Dudley.
-CROW: Attorney.
I'll get him back
on my records again.
MIKE: It's like it's casual day
at 3M.
He's my kind of a salesman,
that boy.
Down, down, down.
-Through a burning ring of...
-Marvelous record.
WHITEY: But what about this?
Which, of course, is the reason
he's now in my ledger.
CROW: No fair.
There was a war.
Strictly a temporary condition.
SERVO: I'll win a Tony one day.
By the slightest excuse,
he will slip back
into his old habit
of taking life easy,
the way a smart salesman should.
You're talking
through your horns again.
Wouldn't want to make a little
bet on that now, would you?
WHITEY: Like what?
Oh, say...
SERVO: A dollar?
A new set of asbestos points
for my pitch fork against...
You'd think Hell
would just provide those?
...a new set of strings
for that thing.
Hmm, on the level?
Strictly on the level.
Of course
if you're afraid, then...
SERVO: I'll become Dr. Smith.
I don't frighten easily.
-Go on.
-That one's turning blue.
Can we have some heat, please?
Well, now, suppose an attractive
young lady
were to ride the route
with this Bill Dudley.
-SERVO: Yes.
-Say she's a magazine writer
and is after material
for an article.
Say
she makes fun
of the way he works.
SERVO: Say I'm starring
in Forever Plaid.
That's all it would take
to get him back into my way
of selling again.
-Yeah.
-You think so, huh?
I'm willing to bet on it.
Hmm, so I get it,
but how could we, up here,
fix it so that a magazine writer
down there?
-Has my dance belt shifted?
-Oh, no.
-No, not me.
-RED: Why not?
The trip will do you good.
MIKE: I'll cover your phones.
Hmm, of course,
I haven't been down there
in a long time.
CROW:
She has a receding hair line.
Even on business.
That's the way to talk.
SERVO: Yeah.
And perhaps,
as a little added distraction
from his work...
SERVO: I'll do community
theater,
I'll make you bigger, stronger.
But perhaps,
something a little more...
MIKE: Mamie Eisenhower-ee?
Ah, never let
the devil dress you.
Oh, perhaps even.
Oh, no, don't you dare.
No magic and no miracles,
it's against the rules.
If I go, I'll go...
like this.
-How dull.
-SERVO: Undercover angel.
All right, is it a bet?
MIKE: They're operating
under a different theology.
Hmm, all right, it's a bet.
I'll put this Bill Dudley
to the test.
CROW: [ Imitating
Mission Impossible 's music ]
Try new enriched stuff.
MIKE: I just saw Howard Hughes
in the desert.
Let me see if I got this
whole thing straight now.
-You're a writer?
-Mm-hmm.
And you wanna do an article
on modern food merchandising.
That's right.
SERVO: And you work
for the devil.
...okay for you to ride
with me today?
CROWD: And it's the '50s.
Well, it's okay with me, then.
But I'd sure have a tough time
making my wife
believe this one.
Well, so would I.
Come on.
SERVO:
Well, you can bilocate
and assume animal form.
MIKE: Uh-huh.
SERVO: Hmm.
She's gonna blow the lid off the
whole bread wholesaling racket.
She's naming names!
CROW:
Ah, never mind those magazines,
I barely read them.
Except for American
Muscle Woman ,
that's interesting.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Now we unload
the first van
at William Conrad's house.
MIKE: They leave orphaned
bread on people's doorsteps?
[ Mimics baby crying ]
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: Why do they keep
the bread in dresser drawers?
SERVO: This is Charles Kuralt.
I'll leave you now
with images of bread.
All right, my life is hell.
What do you want from me?
MIKE: How do you mess up
at this job?
NARRATOR: Well,
that's how Whitey started out
to prove her point.
But Red was not far behind.
MIKE: That's how Whitey
keeps us down.
Hey, you're not down here
just for the ride, you know.
Start working on the guy.
We got a bet on.
CROW: Even the devil won't go
to The Bronx.
[ Engine revving ]
SERVO: It kind of sucks,
I got to take your notes, lady.
SERVO: Hey, can I split your top
and butter your buns?
Hey, you know this seems to be
an awfully dull job
that you have.
Oh, what gave you that idea?
Wasn't my--
I mean,
well, after all, it is just
a delivery man's job,
-isn't it?
-CROW: Not just.
Young lady, take it from me.
Any guy who thinks
this is just a delivery job
belongs in a coal truck
not a bread route.
SERVO: I'm running you in, lady.
You're under arrest
for impeding bread delivery.
MIKE: Well,
then Mabel said to me,
"Well, why did you wear
those earrings?"
And then we went to Nine West,
but we couldn't find anything
we wanted,
because I have really wide feet.
But sometimes,
I can find stuff at Payless.
Anyhoo, Cindy told me
that Victoria's Secret
was just around the corner,
and she said
they're having a sale,
and she knows
I'm really broke right now.
So, I confronted her and well...
SERVO: You know,
I better call the cops on her.
CROW: I never sat on a
loaf of bread before,
it feels great.
SERVO: Maybe I should take that
job as a Mouseketeer.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: If she doesn't shut up
pretty soon,
I'm gonna stuff her
full of croutons.
SERVO:
Get your buns out of my truck.
CROW: Quit loafing in my van,
you really take the cake.
MIKE: You got a lot of crust
to come around here.
[ Laughs ]
SERVO: Come on, you and me,
mano a mano.
Now, let's take a look
at the lighter side
of wholesale bread delivery.
Deet, dee, deet, boom.
Young lady, you sit there,
and I'll be right back.
MIKE: I need some time alone
with my bread.
Doesn't she look smart?
Today's career gal
in her new fashions from...
Hmm...
The Mahavishnu Orchestra.
Well?
Well,
I told him I thought
he was a dope.
Not to work, but to be the
first one in, every day.
-RED: Good.
-CROW: Stanley.
I told him I thought all this
push on getting good displays,
just a lot of front office talk.
Couldn't have phrased it
better myself.
"Why keep a close check on
how your load's going?"
I said.
"You can always dump it
on the last half dozen stops."
Excellent.
And what did he say?
Nothing.
That's the trouble.
He just sat there listening
and looking very thoughtful.
There, you see?
What did I tell you?
My bet's practically won.
I would've sworn that nothing
could make him
slip back into his
old selling ways.
Uh-oh.
[ Mike mimics ]
BILL: Hmm.
Must be new on the force.
MIKE: I got donuts.
Come back.
You talked, and I've listened.
Now it's my turn.
I talk and you listen.
First of all, take a look.
A loaf of bread.
CROW: Eat every piece.
BILL: An important food,
a healthy food.
And a basic food
that can be served
in more than a hundred
different ways.
-SERVO: Actually, one.
-BILL: And give a look.
Not just one kind of bread.
But a whole variety.
And not only bread.
But a whole variety
of all types of baked goods.
SERVO: Oh.
Are you, by any chance,
trying to say that you think
this business
of yours is important?
That's exactly the way
I feel about it.
MIKE: I have to, it's all I got.
There's something
about that guy's tone of voice
I don't like.
-CROW: It's so butch.
-But just because
we're important in the food
picture, doesn't mean a guy
can sit back
and take it easy on this job.
Why not?
[ Music playing ]
Huh, it's jerks like that
that end up as supervisors.
[ Music playing ]
CROW:
It's the circus of the Devil.
SERVO: No, thanks,
I use toilet paper.
MIKE: If you're gonna
tempt a guy, don't send
Clare Boothe Luce.
SERVO: Please observe silence
while visiting the
bread memorial.
BILL: You know...
MIKE: Sausage.
BILL: ...when I first started
on the route,
I acted like it was nothing more
than a delivery job.
CROW: I don't care.
Take this grocer
goodwill business.
CROW:
There's not an article in this.
Why, I used to go into stores,
and slam doors.
MIKE: Hey, Dr. Giggles.
BILL: Hiya, Duffy old boy.
How's the old miser today?
Counting your gold again, huh?
SERVO: I had a Brooklyn accent,
and a different personality.
[ Bill whistles ]
CROW: When bread wholesalers
terrorize the community.
MIKE: Everybody down,
the bread man is here.
SERVO: I'll do anything you say.
CROW:
Let the reign of terror end.
SERVO: Oh.
MIKE:
That's Christine Jorgensen.
Oh, sorry, Duff.
CROW:
Not the Happy's ripple chips.
So I'm done, huh?
See you again, Duff.
[ Laughs ]
It must've been awful.
Well, maybe it wasn't quite
that bad.
Anyway, today,
I go after a grocer's goodwill,
a little different...
I'll show you.
SERVO: Watch me come on
to a grocer.
-BILL: Morning, Mr. Marco.
-Good morning.
CROW: Ah, just putting
the salmon balls away.
MIKE: Mr. Marco,
you want my coffee ring today?
Sure be a shame
if something bad happened
to your store here.
How are you today?
I'm feeling lousy.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
SERVO:
Because I like you, Mr. Marco.
Hey, something new.
MIKE: It'd be a shame
if this ran over your kid.
Hey, these are pretty slick.
You noticed that, eh?
Sure did.
Now, I bet your customers
will go for them, too.
With my customers,
maybe yes, maybe no.
-We'll see.
-Go on, you know doggone
-well they will.
-CROW: Okay, they will,
-but don't hurt me.
-Be right back.
SERVO: I played it nice
this time.
-See?
-You see?
I want every grocer
on my route thinking...
MIKE: What a moron.
MARCO: That Bill Dudley is okay.
Never slams doors.
Always seems friendly,
always got a smile.
SERVO: What's he on?
MAN: Always interested
in my store,
treats my place with respect.
CROW: What does he want from me?
MAN: Never slams
his trays around,
or makes a nuisance
of himself.
SERVO:
Why can't he leave me alone?
MAN: I like to do business
with salesman like that.
MIKE: But his bread sucks.
BILL: Believe me, building
up goodwill is important.
Without it, you get nowhere
in selling a day.
Look, why don't you stay here
and rest a minute
while I go in
and check the sales?
-Don't run off now.
-Oh, I wouldn't think of it.
CROW: Devil's gonna show up
as a hooker now.
[ Music playing ]
The Mahavishnu Orchestra.
I don't like the way
that guy's yakking.
Well, I do.
-You would.
-MIKE: You're a girl.
You want my opinion?
He's in a rut.
Oh, well, if you want mine,
he's in the groove.
Huh, thanks for the match, lady.
What match? Oh.
Oh, yes.
You're welcome.
Haven't I seen that guy
before somewhere?
Beer wine, wine made
from fresh beer.
Now, I was gonna tell you about
the second bull's-eye of mine.
Plus volume.
One way to go after
it if you use this.
-And this.
-CROW: A hat and a pad.
That, my young lady,
is my business bible.
SERVO: Ah.
BILL: I've got a complete
and up-to-date picture
on every stop on my route.
SERVO: Measurements
of every woman in my routes.
BILL: I know exactly
what sells in each store,
and what doesn't.
I know what new items
I've tried in each stop,
how each one is done.
No guesswork.
The facts are all there,
and they're up-to-date.
MIKE: You're reaching out,
aren't you?
Well, team up these facts
with a little bit of this,
and you can go after plus volume
without the risk
of getting stuck
with a lot of returns.
So a guy gets returns.
So what?
Let the boss worry about him.
Huh.
SERVO:
Going over to Al Lewis' house.
CROW: But why does
the strip club need bread?
Here's something else a fella
can do to get plus volume.
Watch me in here.
[ Car honks ]
MIKE: Oh, no, run.
I can't believe I had to
waste him.
CROW: You didn't have
to shoot him the face.
MIKE: Oops, forgot the bread.
[ Laughs ]
BILL: Say, Mr. O'Connor.
MIKE: Oh, I don't live
with my mother.
BILL:
I'm putting in a half a dozen
of these new sweet doughs.
I noticed they were good
last year,
we're running them again.
CROW: You're telling me
how to run my store?
...I'm sure you wanna keep an
eye on them
and see how they're going.
SERVO: Look, I got a restraining
order on you.
See for yourself
how they good they are.
Well, thanks, Bill.
SERVO: [ Munching noises ]
MIKE: Take it out
of the wrapper first.
SERVO: [ Gulping ] [ Burps ]
You see?
Talking it up
is another key
to getting plus volume.
You can get in a good plug
when you introduce
a new package,
a new product, or a special.
CROW: Yeah, that's how it works.
The more you talk it up,
the better chance
of getting him to push it.
SERVO: And the kids will buy it.
But what was all this mumbo-
jumbo business
with so many of this,
at so much,
and so many of that,
at so much.
It's a nice store.
Oh, the count check.
That's something I always do
before I put the stuff
on the shelves.
Avoids mix-ups later on.
-MIKE: Thanks for the carousel.
-BILL: And this is especially
important in big bakery
departments.
You see, in supermarkets,
there are a lot of bakery
salesmen coming in.
-CROW: They're like roaches.
-BILL: The count check
also reminds the grocer
of what baked goods
of mine he's got to sell.
SERVO: Niels Bohr
buys groceries.
BILL: The better he knows
my products,
the better chance
of getting his help
in selling them.
And that makes
for plus volume for me.
MIKE: That means money.
Money I can cover
my naked butt with.
Third bull's-eye of mine.
Selling displays.
You know...
CROW: I'm filled
with resentment.
...that can be a little rough.
You see,
well, take this route of mine.
I've got all kinds
of bread racks
and display shelves.
Some of them are pips.
I guess other guys' routes
are the same way.
I used to give up easy
on displays.
I had only one rule I followed.
SERVO: Kill or be killed.
BILL: As long as the stuff
didn't fall on the floor
while I was there, it was okay.
-MIKE: I was a sick man.
-BILL: No more, though.
SERVO: Now, I just throw it
on the floor.
And believe me, there's
no trick or mystery to building
good-selling displays.
SERVO: Well, a platypus
could do my job.
Just stack the bread
so the brand name shows best.
And shows off the bread
to best advantage.
MIKE: I love each of my loaves.
And give the specialty loaves
the best display space.
And don't squash bread
to get it in.
If a store is selling more
bread that I got room for
-in my display space...
-CROW: Then we got a problem.
BILL: ...I talk to the grocer
about giving me more room.
Say, near the checkout counters,
or on the counter
next to the register.
SERVO: Maybe I rough him up,
maybe I bust his chops.
Now, baked goods
are impulse items, too.
So I always display them
as near eye-level as I can
so they're easy to see...
-ROM: Pffft.
-...and easy to reach.
MIKE: Never put donuts
next to the kitty litter.
BILL: When you figure
a shopper spends an average
of only 35 seconds
in a baked goods department...
SERVO: Psst, hey, lady.
Eat me.
BILL: ...for your display
to work on them.
SERVO: I'm a specialty bread.
Eat me.
BILL: So display it
within easy reach,
group the items together,
keep from burying any item
out of sight.
CROW: In a shallow grave.
But, you know...
MIKE: Sometimes, I wanna put
a bullet in my skull.
A lot of bread boys
are doing that much,
so how do you get
the jump on them?
SERVO:
Maybe rough them up a little.
With special display
and promotion ideas.
Take the other day.
I noticed a stop on my route
was running a special
on hamburger.
Okay.
So, I talked to the grocer
into including rolls
in a special display
next to the hamburgers.
CROW: It didn't work.
BILL: That's where getting
goodwill pays off.
If you got
the grocer's goodwill,
you can get extra
selling displays in the store
built around special
promotions.
SERVO: Mm-hmm.
-BILL: Picnic displays.
-MIKE: Oh, lovely.
BILL: Especially good
just before holidays
and weekends, and summer.
School lunch idea displays,
especially good in fall.
MIKE: He's going over the edge,
stop him.
BILL: Better breakfast displays.
Or any others that tie
with national promotions.
SERVO: I'm making
over three million a year.
BILL:
Seasonal promotion displays.
Fruitcakes around Thanksgiving
and Christmas.
Hot cross buns and
Easter cakes at Easter time.
MIKE: Funeral breads,
war breads.
BILL:
Displays that suggest ideas
for all types of entertaining.
SERVO: Okay, we'll buy
the bread!
BILL: Now you go with
the banners, and cards,
and streamers, or printed
promotional material I can get.
Anything to give any display
more sell.
CROW: Triumph of the bread.
But all this talk of mine
boils down to just this.
This is a tough business,
a mighty competitive business.
MIKE: I've been shot twice.
But the guy who aims,
for grocer goodwill,
plus volume,
and selling displays...
SERVO: Divided by four.
...they can be a darn
good one, too.
Well, now,
that was quite a speech.
Oh, I'm sorry
if I bored you, I...
Bored me?
Oh, no, no.
Quite the opposite.
-MIKE: You terrified me.
-Tell me, how in the world
do you get
all those things done?
Oh, the whole secret to that
is taking it in small chunks.
CROW: And uppers, dexies,
speed...
BILL: Maybe one week
I'm shooting
for special displays
in ten of my best stops.
Next week, ten more, and so on.
After all,
that's only two a day.
Or maybe my goal
for this week is to spend
a couple of extra minutes
in my biggest volume stops
just to work on goodwill.
SERVO: I steal bikes
on the side.
I always got something cooking
at a few stops.
Always something aimed
at one of these bull's-eyes,
grocer goodwill,
plus volume,
selling displays.
And are you sure nobody
could unsell you
on these things?
Not a chance.
I like the payoff too much.
-MIKE: It's five bucks a week.
-Well, don't you ever slip up?
CROW: You coming on to me?
Sure, I'm just as human
as the next guy.
That's why I keep these
bull's-eyes handy
so that a small slip up
doesn't turn
into a big trip up.
SERVO: Oh.
[ Laughs ]
Well, off to the races.
What do you say?
MIKE: Make sure
you stock your truck up
so that you don't--
well, you know.
CROW: Damn you all,
to my place.
MIKE: Oh, it's gonna turn out
the bread truck driver is Jesus.
SERVO: And another great thing
about bread,
-it's really great, and...
-CROW: Yeah, that's fine.
MIKE: Thank you, hope you
accept bread into your life.
To sell this piece
of tripe to a magazine?
Jeez.
Grocer goodwill.
Plus volume.
-CROW: Fake acting.
-Selling displays.
MIKE: Flamboyant prancing.
Okay, so you won a bet.
But Bill Dudley's just one guy.
WHITEY: Oh, well,
maybe I better drop down
and see some of the other
fellows on your list.
Oh, no, you don't.
SERVO: And I just waxed that.
After all, that was only a bet.
But from now on, I'm gonna
keep a pretty close watch
on these guys.
CROW: Especially
when they're showering.
[ Music playing ]
And so will I.
[ Singing ]
CROW: Okay, Jerry.
Shut off the projector.
SERVO: Huh.
Some broad, eh, guys?
Just kidding, of course.
Look, you wanna remember
the three basic points,
plus factor...
[ Doors closing ]
You know,
after watching that short,
I've come to understand
that with the limited
shelf space available,
I have to put more stock
in the specialty bread.
Yeah, that's right.
You know, you just can't rely
on your sweet doughs anymore.
Nope, it's all going the way
of specialty breads.
Now, in a nutshell,
specialty breads
are all the breads
that aren't white bread.
Yeah, for instance,
here is one
of my specialty breads.
It's a bread that has a shampoo
and conditioner
built right in.
My bread has thousands
of tiny loaves
baked right in.
I have a specialty bread
that's normal bread,
except it comes
to a sharp point.
What if you had a bread
that doubled as a foot ointment?
That would be a specialty bread.
You know,
I have a butter top bread
that's actually studded
with bars of real butter.
Then you my friend
have a specialty bread.
I think what I am learning is
that now more than ever,
it's specialty breads.
ALL: Specialty breads.
We'll be right back.
[ Music playing ]
I understand you're a friend
of Harry March.
MAN: Who's Harry March?
Best safecracker around.
Maybe the best in the business.
-MAN: I never heard of him.
-CROW: Is this the screen test?
Okay.
Just thought you might be
interested in a deal.
MAN: Wait a minute, kid,
what kind of a deal?
MIKE: Those lips, oh.
What difference does it make?
MIKE:
He has a haunting ugliness.
Yeah, I make friends real easy.
What kind of a deal?
CROW: You're drunk.
Forget it.
SERVO: Is this a Warhol film?
A million dollars cash.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: "The Autobiography
of Miss Tom Pittman".
MIKE: This suitcase for hire.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: The Potsy story.
Hey, let me out of here.
"The High School Big Shot."
The real
"High School Big Shot."
MIKE: They open
with such strong imagery.
He's a "High School Big Shot."
SERVO: He's a "Big Shot
in High School."
ALL: Big shot, big shot,
big shot,
big shot, big shot, big shot.
CROW: So the big shot's
in band, big deal.
SERVO: Give me some of 'em
horns, yeah, come on.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: Jack Nickolaus.
CROW: A monkey's gonna
come in and start throwing
that suitcase around.
SERVO: Those two-plus ladies,
The Big Shot,
yes, a Big Shot.
He skips to eat
cause he's a Big Shot.
Some big old Big Shot,
hey.
[ Singing ]
Wow.
Hit me.
MIKE: Or anus.
All right, any questions?
At this point, Hamlet picks up
the skull of Yorick
and delivers the famous speech.
Now, to whom
was this speech delivered?
CROW: Richard Dawson?
SERVO: Fred Sanford?
MIKE: Larry Hovis.
Vince, would you mind answering
the question, please?
MIKE: Look at your mouth.
SERVO: You got such a
funny little mouth...
-Vince.
-MIKE: That nipples, oh.
I'm held more by the question
of Hamlet's madness.
I'm sorry, Mr. Carter, would you
repeat the question, please?
To whom was Hamlet's famous
graveside speech delivered?
I don't know, man.
I didn't catch the name
and address on the envelope.
CROW: Mr. Mouth, please.
That's very amusing, Vince.
I don't think
that your final failing mark
in this course
quite as jocular.
SERVO: Dun, dun, dun,
dun, dun, duh.
Address on the envelope.
Did you hear that?
How's he think of him?
[ Laughs ]
Marvin?
CROW: Jawohl!
MR. CARTER: Would you answer
the question, please?
MIKE: What?
And get beat up again?
CROW: It's not even
that his lips are big.
-Yes, sir, the...
-CROW: Weird.
MARVIN: ...the speech
is from act five,
scene one delivered to Horatio
and the gravedigger.
-SERVO: Hey.
-MR. CARTER: Very good.
If some of the others of you
would emulate Marvin,
concentrate your efforts
toward learning something,
you might all be
a lot better off.
Well, I guess that should be
enough for today.
I just wanna remind you
that your term papers
are due on Wednesday
and for several of you
who are on the borderline,
you might profit
by putting a little extra time
and energy into this paper.
[ Bell ringing ]
CROW: Well, time to go have
better sex than you've ever had
in your whole life, sir.
MIKE: Is that Lincoln
or Dr. Zaius on the wall?
SERVO: We'll meet you by the
lunch room
and we're gonna
pants you, Marvin.
[ Chuckles ]
MIKE: I won't live through
the day, thanks a lot, sir.
Oh, Marvin,
can I see you a second?
-MARVIN: Yes, sir?
-Have you given
any more thought to college?
The term is gonna be over
in a week, you know.
SERVO: You're 28,
you should graduate.
I still haven't made up
my mind what I'm gonna do, sir.
Oh, Marv,
you have so much to offer.
It's a shame if you don't take
advantage of it.
MIKE: You've got a cute shape...
I don't know, sir.
I-- I'd like to go
to college, but--
Well, it costs money,
you know, and...
Yes, I know.
And I'm still working on that
scholarship for you.
I think maybe we'll be able
to figure something out.
I sure hope so.
Thank you, Mr. Carter.
MIKE: Oh, run along,
enjoy your beating, son.
CROW: Hey, liver lips.
...as stupid
as taking care of this.
SERVO: Ow, that's my loafer.
MIKE: He's a cabbage patch
Robert Reed.
SERVO: Oh, he's digging in
his ear, ugh.
CROW: Oh, what is that,
chicken?
Oh, I'm gonna wipe it
on my pants.
-No one will know...
-Hey, fink.
CROW: Huh?
VINCE: What's the idea
of trying to make a fool
-out of me in there?
-MIKE: I thought it went okay.
-...what you mean, Vince.
-Well, fink,
oh, you know what I mean.
Answering that question
like you were
some kind of a king
or something.
SERVO: When he's threatened,
his lips engorge.
-Okay. Vince.
-Look, anytime you think
-you're better than me, we...
-BETTY: Vince,
get your big paws off of him.
CROW: And put them on me.
Hey, when did you start
playing nursemaid
to this creep?
SERVO: Oh, playing nursemaid.
Ever since you started trying
to be Tarzan or somebody.
-That's all right, Betty.
-No, it's not.
Now, get out of here
and leave him alone,
you animal.
Oh, okay, baby,
if you want to play mother.
CROW: Whoa, oh, oh.
I'm not gonna stand
in your way.
SERVO: Not when you're
playing nursemaid.
Can I see you tonight?
No.
I have other plans.
CROW:
I'm sharpening my breasts.
Okay, baby.
If you change your mind,
just give me a call.
MIKE: Oh. Say, you elbowed
me there at the end,
you probably wanna
come back and apologize.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO:
My belt's caught in the tree.
CROW:
Let's go to picture, picture.
You didn't have
to do that, Betty,
maybe he'll get mad
or something.
Look, what do I care?
CROW: Betty, pants.
The world's full
of guys like him.
You're kind of special.
Well, look, I'm serious.
SERVO:
In a completely insincere way.
I've kind of wanted to say this
to you for a long time.
CROW: You've got dandruff
and weird smelling breath.
Betty, you go with Vince.
MIKE: Lombardi.
He's sort of the star
of the whole school.
Boys like Vince
will never amount to anything.
MIKE: Oh, my eyebrows
smell like cheese.
Oh, boy, ugh.
Betty, will you go out with me?
CROW: No, I go out with Vince.
I practically
asked you out, haven't I?
-Would you--? I mean...
-Well, how about tonight?
I thought you said
you were busy tonight.
I'm busy for him.
SERVO: Hope you like
sitting alone in dark rooms.
Oh, sure.
Fine.
Pick me up at 8:00.
Okay. I'll pick you up at 8:00.
MIKE: Does drool bother you?
I'll see you then.
Yeah. Betty...
CROW: Do you have
any extra underpants?
What about Vince?
SERVO: He'll join us later.
Don't worry about Vince.
I can take care of him.
MIKE: I have nothing to say
or feel about this situation.
[ Music playing ]
MAN: Hey, Marv, is that you?
Yeah, pop, it's me.
CROW: [ Makes sounds ]
MIKE:
Marv has Dade City stunned.
Did everything go okay today?
Uh-huh.
MIKE:
Oh, what was it today, son?
Swirly? Book dump?
Tittie twister?
Monkey bump? Wedgie?
Hey. How come you're
getting all dressed up?
I got a date tonight.
Real sharp girl
I met down at Tony's.
Well, I've got
a date tonight, too.
-You do?
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, who with?
Betty Alexander.
CROW: No, really.
-Who?
-Hey.
Hey, she's the best-looking
chick in the whole school,
ain't she?
She sure is.
And what in the world
she's going out with you for?
SERVO: [ Makes noise ]
MIKE: Oh, I'm sorry, loser,
I mean son.
CROW: How's mom, dad?
That's okay, pop.
I know I'm not much
but she likes me.
Gee, kid, fine, fine.
Just a chip off
the old block after all, huh?
MIKE:
Don't ever say that again, dad.
Yeah, I guess so.
SERVO: How else can I scar him?
Son, you have a tiny winky.
Hey, Marv.
CROW: The school called,
everyone hates you.
I was wondering you got
any money on you?
Well, a couple of dollars,
pop, but...
Look, kid,
this is a real fancy girl,
-do you know what I mean?
-SERVO: Uh-huh.
Well, I'm gonna have to take her
out to supper, probably,
and-- well, you know.
I know, pop, but I got
a date tonight myself.
I don't get paid until the 15th.
How much you got?
Well, six dollars
and some change.
I'll tell you what,
we'll split even.
Okay?
SERVO: I love you, dad.
Okay, pop.
SERVO: Oh, and son,
I ate the last can of dog food.
Thanks. Oh, by the way, son,
Merry Christmas.
CROW: You know,
maybe if they sold off
one of those Tiffany lamps.
-SERVO: Nice.
-Oh, by the way,
I think I'm gonna have
a job next week.
-Really?
-Yup.
I met a guy today who's sure
he can put me on full time.
MIKE: Yup, I'm gonna sale
my plasma door-to-door.
It'd be swell, pop.
MIKE: Come into my house,
eat my bananas and mock me?
Hey, don't worry, boy.
I'll hang on to this one.
No more booze for me, I promise.
SERVO: Is beer booze?
Pretty soon we'll have money
enough to get out of this dump.
You can quit
that crummy job of yours
and go to college like you want.
CROW: Then, we'll be married.
Like your mother wanted you to.
MIKE: Before I drank her.
I unscrewed her head
and drank out of her neck, well.
I know, pop.
Thanks, kid.
Have a good time tonight, huh?
You too, pop.
SERVO: Three bucks,
I'm gonna buy a French fry, pop.
MIKE: I love my life.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: So, are we gonna walk
the alleys all night?
I'm sorry, Betty, I was...
Oh, that's okay.
At least it was a good movie.
SERVO: I've never walked
to a drive-in before.
It's just that I-- well,
I have to give some money
-to pop and...
-Oh, just forget it.
I'm having a lovely time.
-Betty...
-SERVO: Can I sniff your bra?
I've got almost a dollar left.
Would you like to have a Coke?
I'd love it.
CROW: Thanks a lot,
Adnan Khashoggi.
SERVO: Levon and the Hawks.
MIKE: Tonight only,
Coke's a dollar-ten.
But this guy grabs this chick
by the neck, see,
and he gives her
a couple of whacks
right across the...
man, he'd like to
knock her head off.
CROW: Hey, come on,
that's a delightful story.
Hey, daddy, you don't dig
my act or something?
What's the matter, Vinny?
That chick Betty bugging you?
No. She don't bug me none.
Yeah. Why should she?
We got so much stuff
around here,
we have to beat it off
with a club.
Yeah, so where's it all here?
Hey, am I seeing right?
MAN: Oh, man,
I don't believe it.
CROW: They beamed down.
MAN: I must be cracking up.
SERVO: How's the German
expressionist date going?
What is she doing
with that fink?
Well...
I thought the zoo closed
at 6:00.
-Yeah?
-CROW: It does but--hey.
So how come you don't want
any animals out for a walk?
Very funny.
CROW:
Special dialogue by Neil Simon.
Look, Betty, I think
we better go on home.
-I've got some homework to do.
-You aren't gonna let these
-big apes scare you away...
-You know it's not that,
it's just that
I got some homework to do.
Okay. Come on.
SERVO: Wetting your pants
is considered homework, right?
Well, good night, boys.
Better stay off the streets
before the dog catcher
sees you
without your licenses.
CROW: To the moon, Alice.
Boy, she sure got
salty in a big hurry.
Where does that
cheap broad come off
talking to us like that?
MIKE: Hey,
that's the cheap broad I love.
Hey, let's follow them
and give them a going over, huh?
SERVO:
People pick a song over there?
The guy in the story
that Burt was telling you.
All right.
You guys stay here.
MIKE: Been a really fun
book club, though.
Hey.
CROW: That's your nail clipper.
I thought you said
that chick didn't move you?
She don't.
Not at all.
SERVO: He is a wonderful
puzzle, isn't he?
MIKE: This place
has all the atmosphere
of a ground round.
CROW: And that's why
The Plague is my favorite book.
Thanks, Marv.
I had a real good time.
SERVO: This is where
Mr. Hooper died.
Hmm.
Well, it would have been
better if I'd had more money.
Next time, maybe.
You mean,
there's gonna be a next time?
Well, if you want it.
-If I want it? Of course, I do.
-MIKE: Oh, and I hate it
-when his face lights up.
-Oh, it's great.
Well, I'm not real smart
or anything.
-I...
-CROW: And I don't have
-any arms.
-...thought I might be
-kind of dull.
-SERVO: What the-- what, huh?
Oh, no, you're not dull.
MIKE:
Remember, I'm into Shakespeare.
-Thanks.
-CROW: Yeah.
Your talk of hemlines
kept me riveted.
Marv, I hate to ask you
for a favor or anything...
Go ahead, anything you want.
-SERVO: Hmm, what, what?
-Well, it's Mr. Carter's
Shakespeare class.
You know,
I'm kind of on the borderline.
If I don't pass this class,
I'm not gonna graduate.
And my old man
would kill me for sure.
Well, if you write
a good term paper, you'll pass.
That's just it.
Though, I don't understand him.
Shakespeare, I mean.
He's so deep.
CROW: Don't smile, no.
I don't know what to do.
You want me
to write a paper for you?
Oh, no, I just thought maybe
you'd help me a little bit.
I don't mind.
It will only take me
a couple of hours.
BETTY: Would you?
I mean, would you really?
SERVO: Our little secret,
my little schatz.
Thanks, Marv.
I'll never forget it.
CROW:
I could write a dissertation,
-series of books...
-Well, good night.
-CROW: ...they'll pop up, too.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
MIKE: Marv? Hello?
SERVO:
Perhaps an analysis of Lear,
10 pages, double spaced?
-Hmm?
-Good night, Betty.
MIKE: Good night, sweet prince.
-Oh, Vince.
-CROW: Will you write
-a paper for me?
-You scared me to death.
Look, what's with you two?
MIKE: Rebooting.
With me and Marv?
SERVO: Come on, I can't hold
this face much longer.
Oh, you can't be serious.
Look, you were with him.
You went out with him
instead of me.
CROW: He had three dollars.
But honey, I just wanted him
to write my term paper for me.
MIKE: Would you write mine
if I kissed him?
You sure that's all?
Well, of course, silly.
You don't think I could
possibly see anything in him,
do you?
SERVO: Well,
if you're just giving him sex
for term papers...
No, I don't think so.
Well, you see, actually,
it's kind of for us.
If I don't pass the course,
I won't graduate.
My parents won't let us
get married or anything.
-CROW: She is a saint.
-Yeah.
-MIKE: Mm-hmm.
-SERVO: Now, would you write
my shop project?
But...
why did you kiss him?
Kiss him?
SERVO: You can't miss his lips.
They just ran into me.
You call that a kiss?
CROW: I think so.
Do I have the wrong word again?
Now, this is what I call a kiss.
SERVO: Oh.
CROW: Vince, smooth as silk.
MIKE: [ Chuckles ]
SERVO: Terry Malloy.
Betty?
CROW: Sorry, I made you
work the docks for our date.
MIKE: What?
Have you ever thought
about marrying anybody?
SERVO: And suffocating them
in a loveless union?
Sure.
You know, I wanted
to marry Rock Hudson once.
But he was taken at the time,
so then I just thought
I'd marry Gary Cooper
and I found out he had
a daughter older than me,
-so...
-I'm serious, Betty.
MIKE:
I know I have a moist face.
SERVO: [ Laughs ]
You know what I'm getting at.
CROW: I think you ought
to marry Vince.
After all Marv, you have
to go to college and everything.
I won't go to college.
I'd get a full-time job.
I bet Mr. Matthews
will put me on for $75 a week.
Seventy-five.
I guess,
I misled you just a little.
I mean, you're sweet,
and smart...
-SERVO: And oily, and...
-BETTY: I think someday
you'll really be
somebody important.
MIKE: You'll be U Thant.
BETTY: Little Betty isn't ready
to settle down
and try and live on $75 a week.
-CROW: Seventy-eight?
-I've been poor
too long for that.
CROW: Eighty?
BETTY:
Oh, look, I'd better be going.
My old man
will be full of questions.
He thinks I'm a tramp.
What's the matter?
You said your father
thinks you're a tramp?
Just when he's feeling good.
If you could hear
some of the things he's--
one night,
when my mom was out...
MIKE: I never completed...
I never finish a...
Someday, I'm gonna show him.
I'm gonna come back here
with my diamonds and my furs.
And I'm gonna throw them
right in his stinkin' face.
CROW: Now, hold still, son.
Marv?
Hmm?
How come you ain't out
with Betty tonight?
No, she wanted
to stay home tonight.
Said it makes her old man happy
if she stays in every
once in a while.
Oh, I see.
SERVO: So,
wanna get a porn movie?
CROW: Really, I think it's time
we consider that suicide pact.
-Look, Marv...
-SERVO: Hey, could you massage
my feet?
What would you say
if I got married again?
SERVO: Well,
you should clear it with mom.
Well, what brought that on, pop?
Well, I figure you'll be
through school soon,
probably be going to college,
or getting married maybe,
and a man's got to
have someone look after him
in his old age.
And I got that job coming up.
CROW: Gonna be town drunk.
Is she the girl you met
down at Tony's, pop?
MIKE: I'm not sure, I think so.
Do you love her?
Oh, she's wonderful, kid.
SERVO: He runs a tilt-a-whirl.
Sweet as pie,
you know what I mean?
CROW: And twice as fattening.
Who're you trying
to convince, me or you?
No, really.
She's different.
MIKE: She has an extra hip,
really disturbing.
Pop, if you got married,
you'd have to hold a job.
I would, boy.
I'd do anything
in the world for her.
CROW: Isn't unemployment a job?
Well, I guess
you love her, then.
SERVO: Not as such, no.
-Would you mind?
-MIKE: getting off my foot?
No.
I think it's great.
When's the big day?
CROW: Well, you see, son,
she lives in the thimble kingdom
and she has to defend
the mushroom people
before we can marry.
That isn't settled.
SERVO: Her name is Thimbelina.
By the way,
she milks butterflies
and she's charmed,
if I touch her, I turn to wood.
[ Chuckles ]
Pop, have you asked her yet?
Fact is, I haven't, but
that won't be no problem, boy.
-I can tell.
-MIKE: Once I'm elevated
to full dwarfdom.
I'm real happy for you, pop.
CROW: Then join us
at the emerald gathering.
-SERVO: Well, okay.
-MIKE: Oh, yeah.
I guess, there's nothing
in the whole world
as nice as being in love.
[ Music playing ]
Boy, it sure is quiet.
I wonder where everyone is.
Uh-oh.
[ Car engine revving ]
[ Crow hooting ]
Whoa, ow, oh,
ah, ha, ha.
Hey, you guys, get back here.
I mean it.
Are you talking to us,
Mr. Nelson?
Yeah, something wrong,
Yeah. You got a problem,
Mr. Nel Stupid?
Yeah. I got a problem.
What you did was so wrong.
Oh, no.
Please enlighten us.
-Yeah.
-Well, you see,
when you egg someone,
you're supposed to do
raw eggs not omelets,
you morons!
Raw eggs? What a laugh.
Huh, squaresville, man.
Strictly squaresville here.
So long, daddy-o.
[ Laughs ]
Who needs?
I can't believe they did that,
even they should know
that was wrong.
SERVO: Hey, old man Nelson,
didn't like the omelets, huh?
CROW: Then, try this.
[ Laughing ]
Oh.
Hey, guys, get back here.
What now, father time?
Well, you see, your Hollandaise
is way too lemony.
Oh, too bad.
Oh, no, we got movie sign.
[ Indistinct chatter ]
BOTH: [ Laughing ]
[ Doors opening ]
MIKE: Real funny.
Real funny.
Hiya, Kid.
Hi, Mr. Matthews.
MIKE:
Therefore, I petition the court
that my father be
committed and...
CROW: Oh, I'm gonna catch
that Abbott and Costello.
We've got another deal goin'.
How much is involved?
A million dollars, cash.
SERVO: Oh, where's
the million-dollar file?
MIKE: Ah, here it is.
CROW:
Shipping clerk work khakis.
[ Knocks on door ]
SERVO: Are you decent?
-Yes.
-Excuse me, Mr. Matthews.
You wanna sign these papers?
Later, kid, I'm real busy.
-Okay.
-CROW: Oh, they sort of
built up but...
We've handled some big deals
before, Walt,
but never a million dollars.
CROW: Watch the bowling balls,
coming through.
Sorry, kid.
MAN: ...this much heroin before.
MATTHEWS: What's our cut?
MAN: Twenty-five percent.
-MATTHEWS: Good enough.
-SERVO: You're getting this
out there, Marvin?
Boat's due in Saturday night.
The money will arrive here
sometime this afternoon.
MAN: Who's bringing it in?
MATTHEWS: Never mind.
It's coming,
you can rest assured.
And I'll put it in the safe.
And at exactly 11:15,
I'll be back with the guy
carrying the dope.
I'll give him the money
and they'll make the exchange.
Isn't it a little risky
leaving a million dollars
in the safe that long?
Nobody will know it's there.
-SERVO: I do.
-And I'd rather have it here
than carry it around
if you follow me.
Sure.
Now, all you have to do
is open the doors
for us at 11:15
and then standby to make sure
that there's no double cross.
Okay. You know, that's it.
CROW: Oh, the big heroin
shipment is coming down
the street.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: A million dollars.
that's 75 bucks a week for life!
I'll see you there.
Take it easy.
CROW: Good luck with the heroin.
Kid. Kid!
Yes, sir.
Let me have a look
at those papers.
MIKE: Oh, heroin I come.
SERVO: Oh.
CROW: Wait, they all had
to go to the bathroom?
I'm very disappointed
in you, Marv.
CROW: It's been two weeks
and you haven't slipped
her the tongue yet.
I don't understand, Mr. Carter.
I think you do.
MIKE: Okay. You're excused.
Well, we might as well
get this over with
as quickly as possible.
CROW: I'm not Robert Q. Lewis.
He wrote your paper,
didn't he?
He--
of course not,
I wrote it myself.
Oh, come now, Betty.
You have many attributes,
I will confess.
-SERVO: Oh.
-CARTER: But a comprehensive
understanding of Shakespeare
and his works
is not one of them.
I studied.
I worked real hard.
MIKE: James at 16.
Well, Marv,
you wanna tell me the truth?
SERVO: Well, sir,
everyone thinks
you smell like old hamburger.
Uh-oh.
She wrote it, honest,
Mr. Carter.
CROW: Am I a Sweathog now,
Mr. Kotter?
MIKE: [ Chuckles ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
of the jury,
-we are asked to believe...
-CARTER: All right then,
what is it all about?
SERVO: Oh, um, well,
there's this plot,
and there's people and a lot
of betwixt other stuff
and forsoothing.
-Oh.
-It's about Shakespeare
and his plays.
CROW: She did write the paper.
You didn't even read it,
did you?
Of course, I read it.
I wrote it.
Now, look, neither one of you
is fooling anybody
but yourselves.
Now, come on, Marv,
admit it and get it over with.
MIKE: She's guilty
of thought crimes.
-CARTER: Come on.
-MIKE: Put the rat mask on her.
SERVO: [ Chuckles ]
Yes, sir.
That's better now.
-SERVO: Abe, your witness.
-You didn't have to tell him.
He couldn't prove it.
I hope you understand
that I'll have to fail you
for this, Betty.
As far as you're concerned,
Marv,
your grades are too good.
I can't possibly fail you.
CROW:
I'm out of those little slips.
I can't even blame you...
But I am going to withdraw
my recommendation
for the scholarship.
I thought that you were
different, Marv.
But, I guess I was wrong.
You don't deserve
that scholarship
and you know it.
You're just bitter
because you can't do anything
but earn 60 bucks a week
with your fancy words
and big brains.
You have no right to flunk me.
CROW:
Don't stand so close to me.
[ Gasps ]
That's all you're worried about.
You don't even care
that Marv may lose
his opportunity
to go to college because of you.
SERVO: You temptress,
parading around
in that revealing sweater.
Sorceress.
All right.
That's all. You're both excused.
MIKE: But Betty, Marv
is more excused than you.
MARV: Betty.
-Betty.
-Look, stay away from me,
-you fink.
-Betty.
Look, you didn't have
to tell him.
-But he knew.
-He didn't know.
-He couldn't prove it.
-SERVO: Betty, Betty.
Betty, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Well, be sorry somewhere else
and just leave me alone.
CROW: Do you know
where the office is?
You mean it's over
just because of this?
-SERVO: Betty.
-Over?
Now, what's there to be over?
SERVO: But, Betty...
Well, I thought you said that...
Look, I didn't say anything.
MIKE: Oh, Betty?
You did all the talking,
remember?
SERVO: Betty.
♪ What kind of fool am I? ♪
Oh, wow, you were just using me.
CROW: Ding, ding, ding, ding.
We have a winner.
That's right.
SERVO: Oh, you want me
to sign your yearbook?
Look, all I know is now, I'm...
CROW: Lola Falana.
My father is gonna kill me,
he really will,
and I'm not
gonna graduate and...
MIKE: Because I'll be dead
because he killed me.
I guess things just don't
wanna work out for me.
Betty.
SERVO: Can I still
call you Betty, Betty?
Betty, you said
that you wanted to come back
and throw diamonds
and minks in his face.
So?
CROW: Are they live minks?
So if I could get
those things for you...
MIKE: Oh, sorry. A little
bratwurst repeating on me.
And the way you feel,
I mean, about the whole world.
Thanks, Marv, but it won't help.
I mean it, Betty.
Could it make a difference?
Well, bring them around
the first chance you get.
It might make
a difference at that.
SERVO: I have my answer.
I'm walking on air.
MATTHEWS: I'll put it in
the safe.
MAN: Isn't it a little risky,
leaving a million dollars
in the safe that long?
CROW: Where, oh, where
could a guy find a bell tower?
Mm-hmm.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: At least there's dad
to cheer me up.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Dad,
I've told you, not on the rug!
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Oh, dad's turned
into Gregor Samsa.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO:
Mm-hmm. Suspense. I can't wait.
It's gonna be so cool
when they reveal it.
I just can't-- oh.
MIKE: Dad's new girlfriend
is named Smirnoff.
SERVO: Why, no one can spend
three bucks the way dad does.
CROW: This is so beautiful.
MIKE: Boy, it's like
a Norman Rockwell painting.
SERVO: You didn't leave
any for me, you jerk.
Why, pop?
You said you were through.
MIKE:
Well, it's empty, isn't it?
Gonna lecture me again?
CROW: You're grounded.
SERVO: Might as well have
Mitchell for a dad.
CROW: Well, Happy Easter anyway.
MIKE: The Big Brother program
doesn't work for everybody.
What happened, pop?
SERVO: I opened the bottle
and drank some.
She turned me down.
-SERVO: Why?
-MIKE: Why?
I ain't good enough for her--
ain't got enough dough.
-CROW: Oh, it's her fault.
-They're all alike.
Only thing they want is money.
SERVO: My body isn't enough.
MIKE: What would you
at home do?
SERVO: You have pimples.
Execute them.
MATHEWS:
Nobody will know it's there.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Are those voices
in your head or mine?
Pop, I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
-You're going to see that...
-No, I'm not gonna see
that girl again.
She's just like all the rest,
you'll see.
Lay down, pop.
I'll be right back.
SERVO: Just stay there
and hallucinate.
MIKE: Oh, not on our
one piece of furniture.
-Marv...
-SERVO: Ugh.
...don't go.
You're my son, you're all
I got left in the world.
CROW: Besides my lucky table.
MIKE: You know, the thing is,
he isn't even close
to hitting bottom.
-SERVO: Mm-mmm.
-Come on, pop.
I'll help you on the sofa.
SERVO: Come on.
Let's change that diaper.
CROW: Dad, come on.
We've got our Webelos meeting.
See you right back, pop.
When I get back,
maybe we can show them all
a thing or two.
SERVO: Pop? Pop.
Pop. Oh, my God.
Come on, pop. Live.
Damn it. Live.
MIKE: Hand me the remote, son.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Meanwhile,
Betty, earns some extra credit
after school.
CROW: Van Cliburn
entertains a groupie.
Boy, if the class
could see me now.
CROW: We can!
They'd just be jealous,
that's all.
-Honey, I don't know if...
-MIKE: My hands are stuck
-to your head.
-Well, you know,
I'm supposed to be so hard
and tough and all.
Tell me you love me.
SERVO: You love me.
I love you.
Again.
CROW: I can't hear you, worm.
I love you, baby.
I love you.
When are you gonna prove it?
MIKE: Oh,
should I give you a deposition?
Prove it?
You mean, you don't believe me?
Oh, I believe it.
But a girl likes to see
something real, you know.
SERVO:
Something in a mutual fund.
What do you mean?
Like a car or jewels
or something?
Oh, or something.
CROW: Like a supersoaker
in a nudie suit.
You'll have it all
someday, baby.
I swear it, you'll have it all.
When?
-Soon.
-CROW: How's Thursday?
When I got out of school
and have a chance
to look around a little.
SERVO:
Inventing the desktop computer.
Now, what if someone comes along
who already has it?
CROW: Stuff and stuff.
I'd kill him and take it away.
SERVO:
That is correct. Let's move on
to the lightning round.
Tell me again.
SERVO: I forgot what I said.
I love you, baby.
CROW: There's that Vince magic.
SERVO: He's gonna bowl
his troubles away.
MIKE: The mean streets
of Appleton.
Hey, I'm fake-walking here.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: He's surveying
his liquor kingdom.
It's Gigot.
I think the point-
of-purchase displays
have gotten
a little out of hand.
SERVO:
Where's the bread display?
[ Music playing ]
MIKE:
Here's one of the great one's
classic routines.
CROW: [ Laughs ]
It's the all impulse item store.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: It's nutty, huh.
MIKE: Tonight,
on Lou Jacobi Playhouse.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Ooh, that's good booze.
SERVO: And now back to our show.
Get your mitts
out of my register.
Samuel, please, my most
valuable possessions.
Sure, for stealing my cigars,
drinking my wine,
and dipping
into my cash register.
Samuel, I'm shocked.
Your own flesh and blood.
SERVO: Mostly flesh.
My what?
Just because
I'm married to your sister
doesn't give you
cause to come in
and nail my inventory.
Well, she's your wife,
isn't she?
-Yeah, but...
-And she's my sister.
-Sure.
-Then you admit it,
what yours is mine.
CROW:
I like this new movie better.
Look, I don't wanna be a nag.
Why don't you go get a job?
A job? Would you have
a doctor take up a pick?
A chemist sit
behind the wheel of a truck?
If he was making a bum
out of me, I would.
Samuel, I'm a professional man.
There's no other way.
Now, you were in the rackets,
you ought to know that.
Yeah, but I gave it up
10 years ago.
[ Phone ringing ]
CROW: I hope that's
the scene police calling.
SAMUEL: Sam's.
Hello?
Yeah.
Yeah, dear.
-Potatoes?
-SERVO: Potatoes, tomatoes,
-tomatoes?
-Bread?
Yeah, I'll pick it up.
No, I won't forget.
Yeah, good bye, dear.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye-bye.
CROW: Damn Jerky Boys.
Your sister.
Your wife.
Samuel, you are the last
of the great gentlemen.
Have a cigar.
SERVO: Early Edmonds and
Curly isn't that good.
MIKE: Real nice art direction.
CROW: Mm-hmm, you can't
art direct those stains
on the wall.
Hit it, punk.
You ain't old enough.
I'm not here to buy liquor.
Sorry, we're fresh out of Cokes.
Are you Sam Tolman?
Yeah. So?
SERVO: I need a bottle adapter
for my lips.
I understand you're a friend
of Harry March.
Harry March?
Who's Harry March?
MIKE: Am I in the right movie?
The best safe cracker around,
maybe the best in the business.
Never heard of him.
Okay. I just thought you might
be interested in a deal.
Wait a minute, kid.
-CROW: Is that your real face?
-What kind of a deal?
What difference does it make?
You said you didn't know him.
I make friends real easy.
What kind of a deal?
MIKE: I haven't figured
that part out yet.
A big deal.
CROW: Oh, I'm in.
A million dollars cash.
A million dollars cash?
Kid, I'm busy, why don't
you go tell your fairy tales
-someplace else?
-I mean it, a million cash.
And so where is it?
Maybe it's in the Mint
or maybe it's in Fort Knox?
It's about six blocks from here.
You're lying.
Look, I know where the money is
and I know how to get it.
All I need is someone
that could open a safe.
So you ain't lying?
How does a punk like you
know where a million dollars is?
SERVO:
I, sir, am a shipping clerk.
Mr. Tolman, all my life,
my brains have been
sort of a curse.
CROW: Unlike Dick Cavett.
Now, maybe I can make
it pay off for everybody.
MIKE: Hmm,
chin needs a quick cleaning.
Let's say that you know
where the million is
and let's say you have
a plan how to get it.
Where do I come in?
And Harry.
CROW:
Well, we'll need a pony keg.
Well, you just tell Harry
to be here tomorrow night
at 8:00.
I'll explain it then.
Okay, kid, I'll have him here,
but...
if you're lying...
SERVO: Oh, how droll.
I've already had
one beating today.
I don't suppose
another one would kill me.
SERVO: Oh, I know you.
You're that Shakespeare Queen
that Betty dumped.
MIKE: Man, this chin is filthy.
Well,
where is your young genius?
He said 8:00.
It's only a few minutes after.
I'm surprised at you, Samuel.
This is obviously
somebody's idea of a joke.
Look, that's what
I thought at first,
but I could swear
he was on the level
after talking to him awhile.
If there were a million dollars
hanging about someplace,
every operator in the country
would know about it.
Maybe so, but...
[ Knocks on door ]
-MIKE: Stay in there, mom.
-That's him now.
SERVO: Eddie
Chayefsky's House of Games.
CROW: Hmm, good reefer, man.
[ Coughs ]
Here he is, Harry.
SERVO: Grab his pickle.
Marv Grant.
SERVO: I'm kind
of clammy, so be careful.
Harry March.
CROW: Well, I better get back
to social studies.
Glad to meet you, Mr. March.
I've heard
quite a bit about you.
All good, I might add,
depending on which side
of the law you hold with.
Thank you.
Gentlemen,
let's not be so polite.
I can't keep the store
closed forever.
-I gotta make a living.
-Okay. Sit down.
-I'll explain it to you.
-CROW: We find out
where they store the band candy
-and we steal it.
-Now, tomorrow night,
there's a freighter docking
at the pier.
The Rose Lee out of Hong Kong.
SAMUEL: So?
SERVO: Oh, you're right,
I don't know.
There's a shipment
of pure heroin being smuggled in
on that ship for delivery here.
Wait a minute.
I refuse to have anything
to do with narcotics.
Besides, it's a federal rap.
Yeah, besides,
you said it was cash.
I'm getting to that.
Now a syndicate here has
agreed to take the heroin off
the hands of the present owners
for a million dollars cash.
Relieving them of the risks
and the headaches
of distributing
and selling the stuff.
So we grab the million
before it gets to the guys
with the junk.
Exactly.
One million dollars
in untraceable, unmarked...
-CROW: Pennies.
-...probably highly
ill-gotten cash.
Very well.
So far, so good.
Now, what about our cut?
For Sam and me.
Fifty-five, forty-five.
SERVO:
♪ If man is still alive... ♪
Take it or leave it.
We'll take it.
Now, what's the set-up?
Walter Mathews
is the middleman.
He's the guy that owns the
warehouse on the dock, huh?
Right.
The million dollars will be
in his safe sometime tomorrow.
At 11:15, Mathews
and the dope owner arrive
to exchange the heroin
for the cash.
But by then,
we'll have the cash.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Hi, this is Marv.
Is your million dollars in yet?
BETTY: Hello?
Hello, Betty, this is Marv.
-Please don't hang up on me.
-No, thanks.
I thought I made myself
pretty clear.
Please, Betty,
this is important.
SERVO: I think I made a mistake
in that paper I wrote.
Not on the phone.
Can you meet me somewhere?
CROW: When what freezes over.
Money, Betty.
SERVO:
Sweet, buttery money.
MARV: Money to buy you
everything you've ever wanted.
MIKE: Hello?
Whose turn is it to talk?
-Are you there, Betty?
-Look, is this a gag?
-I hope to die if it is.
-CROW: I hope to die anyway.
BETTY: Where do you want me
to meet you?
Joe's Diner, 7th and Adams.
BETTY: Okay. Good-bye.
Good-bye.
SERVO: Geez, I just planned
my heist and my date
for the same night!
CROW: Hmm. Hard Rock Cafe's
just don't work everywhere.
MIKE: Uh-uh.
SERVO: [ Humming ]
Edward Hopper's Night Dorks.
CROW: Is there
a Marv here-- uh-oh.
Stick with me, baby,
and we'll go to places like this
every night!
SERVO: Don't have the meatloaf.
Would you like some coffee?
-CROW: I can afford it.
-No.
Let's just get to the point.
MIKE: That was my point,
actually.
I'm gonna get
some money, Betty.
Oh, really?
How much?
Lots.
CROW: A berdillion,
kajillion dollars.
Enough to buy you all
the diamonds and mink coats
in the whole world.
SERVO: If they cost less
than three dollars.
Boss make you president
of the company or something?
No, but I'm getting it,
I swear it.
Well, did you get me all the
way down here just to talk...
SERVO:
I was gonna stare at you, too.
Now, where are you getting
this fortune?
CROW: Can anyone here be
tempted with a little dessert?
This guy gives awkward
adolescence a bad name.
SERVO: Yeah, I managed
to get us a table.
MIKE: Would you just
say something?
-I'm stealing it.
-SERVO: I think.
You're what?
SERVO: I'm not stealing it?
Oh, look, cut it out, will you?
You haven't even got
the nerve to lie.
I mean it, Betty, I'm stealing
a million dollars.
CROW: I'm stealing it
a dollar at a time
from a million places.
Look, you shouldn't joke
about these things, Marv.
I'm not joking.
I found out where there's
gonna be a million dollars cash
and I worked out a plan
to steal it.
CROW: And then we're taking
a chariot to Mars.
You're really serious,
aren't you?
SERVO: I just put my arm in pie.
You'd really do that for me?
SERVO: Yes, I'm that screwed up.
[ Laughs ]
Betty.
CROW:
Your chair is on my foot.
I'm in love with you.
SERVO: ♪ When you're in love
with a beautiful woman ♪
I know I can.
I've got the best safe cracker
in the business
-lined up to do it with me.
-When?
Saturday night
at the warehouse.
We'll have to split
with the other guys,
but there'll be over
half a million for us.
SERVO: But, unfortunately,
I've hired 500,000 guys to help.
I could have everything
I've ever dreamed of.
SERVO: A pony, an ironing board,
and some stirrup pants.
I could finally spit
in his face.
SERVO: But first I'll eat a bag
of Oreos and a Snickers bar.
You're crazy.
MIKE: Iago was clearly
representational of the devil
for at one time Othello looked
for his cloven hooves.
You're out of your mind.
Oh, am I?
Listen, mister,
I'm giving you a break
you haven't got coming.
A break?
Asking me to heist
a million bucks from guys
who'll be armed to the teeth?
So who says you can't carry
a gun yourself?
SERVO: My dad.
Oh, I never have.
Look, I've copped radios,
hub caps, stuff like that,
but I'm no operator.
CROW: I'm a small-time loser.
So what are you, then?
MIKE:
I am muscular dystrophy.
SERVO: You're always one step
ahead of me.
Look, honey, it'll be a cinch.
All you have to do is grab them
when they come out
-with the money.
-SERVO: What?
Look, you can get Larry
and Burt to help you.
You don't have to tell them
how much it is.
CROW: Larry Bird's
gonna help them?
-SERVO: Hmm?
-Look, aren't I worth it?
SERVO: Uh...
I don't know.
Oh, let me clue you, buster,
I'm getting out of this dump
one way or the other.
SERVO: Why did they meet
at the dump?
Now, if you want me to go
with Marv, that's okay,
but I'm giving you
the chance to take me.
-CROW: Oh.
-SERVO: Hmm, oh, oh, God.
I have to take a cold shower.
Quit following me!
CROW: This movie is low
on linguistic synapses.
You wouldn't go with him,
no, not really.
Wouldn't I?
If I have a million bucks,
I'd go with anyone.
SERVO: Tom Arnold, Haile
Selassie, Soupy Sales, Idi Amin,
-Abe Vigoda.
-Are you in love with him?
Now what's love got
to do with it?
SERVO: What's love, but a second
hand emotion to man.
[ Crow beatboxing ]
I don't know.
CROW: Want some gum?
SERVO: Always hard when I have
to think and stuff.
Look, Vince,
I want you, I really do.
SERVO: Baby, I'mma want you.
I wanted you for years
and you know it.
-CROW: But you weren't home.
-But I want something else too.
SERVO:
Maintenance free vinyl siding.
And maybe more than
I want you, even.
And if I can have them both,
that's great,
but if I have to choose...
MIKE: Boy, this movie
is filled to the brim with chin.
[ Crow giggling ]
SERVO: Vincent Suave Overdrive.
[ Humming ]
CROW: Oh, wow, it's all soft
and stuff when we kiss.
Will you do it?
SERVO: I thought I was.
-Okay.
-MIKE: Vince do it.
CROW: I get it, sex metaphor.
SERVO: Is he a shipping clerk?
Package here
for Mr. Matthews.
Okay. I'll see he gets it.
MIKE: Are you a real lonely guy?
SERVO: Oh, yeah. You?
MIKE: Yeah. Yup.
Me, too, yup.
-Yup.
-Okay, buddy, thanks.
CROW: Oh, finally, his cheese
and sausage gift pack
from Hickory Farms
has arrived.
Hey, kid.
SERVO: I don't have your money.
-For me?
-Yes, sir. It is.
Bring it in here, huh?
SERVO: Boss is always
in a good mood
when the heroin arrives.
CROW: It's a Ma Kettle
blow up, doll.
[ Laughs ]
[ Mike Laughs ]
SERVO: I thought these back
issues of Video Watchdog
would never come.
MIKE: So, Mr. Peepers
is a heroin dealer?
CROW: Mm-hmm.
Hmm, uh-uh.
Kal Kan is better.
SERVO: Hi, son,
how'd the robbery go?
Gee, pop, beans?
It's all we got in the house.
You want a bite?
No, you finish it.
-SERVO: Don't tempt me.
-You going out?
Uh-huh.
Well, don't you have
some homework?
Pop, it's Saturday night.
Remember,
school finished Friday.
Oh, sure, yeah.
I keep forgetting.
CROW: Are we still on
for my sponge bath, son?
You got a date?
Yeah, sort of.
-Marv.
-Hmm?
Did you get your check?
MARV: Pop, I don't get paid
until the 15th,
you know that.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
CROW: Ah.
It's just that Mrs. Fisher's
coming up for the rent tonight
and I was wondering...
MIKE: If I could pay her
in cash instead of sex.
MARV: You blew your job,
didn't you?
SERVO: Oh, just got
a big hunk of pork.
MARV: What happened, pop?
He reconsidered, said
he guessed I was too old.
-CROW: Hmm.
-I don't know what to do, boy.
Everywhere I turn,
the same thing happens.
CROW: I get drunk,
vomit, pass out,
and don't get hired.
SERVO: Dad, I don't wanna be
around when the beans kick in.
Pop, everything's
gonna be all right.
It ain't fair to you kid.
No, it's true, I'm a burden.
If I weren't around,
you could do anything you want,
live your life the way you want,
go to college, like...
Look, pop, I don't want you
talking like that anymore,
you understand?
-SERVO: I mean you're right.
-Marv.
Listen.
CROW: Can you borrow me
some bean money?
I want you to know one thing.
SERVO: I'm your mother.
No matter what happens,
I want you to know I tried
to be a good father to you,
really, I tried.
SERVO: Do you have
any specific examples?
You're the best father
a kid ever had.
Maybe I don't iron
your shirts too good, but...
-Pop.
-Yeah?
MIKE: You're standing
on my foot.
Everything's gonna be
all right, pop.
Sure. Sure.
-You okay?
-Sure.
-No more booze.
-Oh, no.
Now, look, get going,
you'd be late.
Have a good time tonight, kid.
Stay out of trouble, huh?
Sure, pop.
SERVO: Who is he?
I know I should know him.
Remember what I said, pop,
everything's gonna be all right.
Sure, I'll remember.
Hmm.
CROW: Everything is gonna be--
every bean is beans.
Come here you, little rascals.
[ Laughs ]
[ Servo makes a fart sound ]
SERVO: Come on, I'm alone,
geez, what do you want?
Sure.
I'll remember.
[ Doors closing ]
Crow, Crow rendezvous
at targets.
-Crow.
-CROW: Ah, it is I,
T. Hewitt Edward Crow,
stealthily, like a cat--oh, oh.
-Fine.
-Sorry, Cat.
We have
to get pass this lock
if we wanna read Gypsy's diary.
Ah, the simplest of tasks
for T. Hewitt Edward Crow.
Turn the dial left 22, right...
-Crow, it's a key lock.
-Hmm?
-Oh.
-Can we just use the dynamite,
please?
I agree, like a cat, dynamite.
Right.
Fire in the hole!
[ Explosion ]
[ Coughing ]
Look at that, still locked.
Any ideas, T. Hewitt?
Ah, more dynamite.
-Right, more dynamite.
-Yes.
The answer is clear.
Delicate application of TNT,
-precisely calibrated.
-All right. Fire in the hole.
Okay.
[ Explosion ]
[ Coughing ]
Oh, wow.
It's still locked.
Hey, you wanna give it
another go?
-Ah, sure, what the heck.
-Okay.
[ Coughing ]
Tough. Boy, I tell you,
these Happy Hearts diaries
are really well-made.
Fire in the hole.
[ Explosion ]
SERVO: This is really
frustrating.
[ Coughing ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Humming ]
That's five in a row.
Are you cheating?
Honor, Sam.
Remember, honor.
Oh, yeah, sure.
CROW: I wish this movie
had these two guys in it.
About six thou.
Peanuts.
-SERVO: Hmm?
-MIKE: It's a low key
-laid back heist.
-SERVO: Mm-hmm.
But don't edit,
whatever you do.
CROW: Mm-hmm.
Hello, new dads.
-Hello, son.
-Hi, Harry.
SERVO: It's like you got
yourself Old Maid.
Who's winning?
He's killing me.
Did you fix these cards?
I told you repeatedly, Samuel,
I am a thief, not a crook.
[ Laughing ]
-[ Indistinct ] the same?
-Mm-hmm.
SERVO: Just deal, Nicky
Arnstein.
Throw the seven.
Go on.
CROW: Hmm, Rhea Perlman.
SERVO: Never seen Marv happier.
Gin.
SERVO: What is he--wait,
we've been playing poker.
CROW: The most
affable thugs ever.
-SERVO: Mm-hmm.
-Figure it up.
[ Sighs ]
SERVO: Avoris, anyone?
Well, you fellows have any plans
what you gonna do
with your share of the money?
SERVO: Marv's gonna buy
a fresh dad.
We had some good things
coming for a long time.
You know, I think
anybody that sticks with me
all these years is...
gotta get a break.
You're not so bad, Sam.
How about you, Marvin?
-Me?
-CROW: I'm gonna blow it all
-on video games.
-Oh, I'm gonna get married,
go to school.
-College?
-Mm-hmm.
You know, I have always had
a lust for education myself.
I wonder
if they'd let me in somewhere,
that is, if I had enough money.
Sure. You could teach the kids
to rob the professor's desk
and steal the exams.
You're snide, son,
but you are my flesh and blood.
-SERVO: In law.
-Let's play a little Hearts.
We have some time to kill.
Okay. But let's keep
the stakes low.
I don't trust him
and you're too smart.
Oh. High card deals.
[ Tom humming ]
CROW: Meanwhile,
in the same room, across town...
...shock.
Anything, pops. Lay it on me.
MIKE: I'm pregnant.
We're gonna get ourselves
50,000 bucks tonight.
What are you smoking?
I'm serious.
-SERVO: Opium, but I'm serious.
-Dead serious.
We can get it,
if you guys got the guts.
For that kind of dough, I got
guts I ain't even used yet.
What's the scam?
CROW: We take your guts
and harvest your organs.
Okay, now, you guys hear me
and hear me good.
SERVO:
If they were a lot smarter,
they can be the Bowery Boys.
Now you're not gonna
believe half of this,
none of it maybe,
but it's all true.
Now, there's gonna be
a safe robbery tonight,
not more than three blocks
from here.
Now, I know who's pulling it,
and I know what we gotta do.
[ Imitating monkey sounds ]
All we do is wait for them
to come out with the loot,
and then we grab it.
-It's so easy, it scares me.
-Who?
Who's doing it?
Who told you?
SERVO: Guess.
Marv Grant.
Oh, come on, Vince,
quit putting us on.
I'm telling you.
SERVO: Okay, it was Marv Albert.
You mean all we gotta do
is walk up,
and take it?
That's right.
SERVO: No, no way,
it's too complicated.
With these.
CROW:
Oh, he's the Vasectomy Kid.
Why can't I attract real dames
like I attract this lousy
queen of spades?
SERVO: Because they
don't wanna be torn in half.
It's almost quarter of,
let's get going, huh?
No.
I don't wanna leave
until exactly 10:45.
Why can't we leave now?
Why do you have
to cut it so fine?
Look, I timed the ride
a dozen times,
it takes exactly 11 minutes to
get from here to the warehouse.
CROW: Come on, who's the
high school junior around here?
[ Tom chuckles ]
Besides I don't wanna arrive
at the ferryboat
until exactly 10:52.
SERVO: Don't pay the ferryboats.
Very well.
SERVO: Hey, here's my
impersonation of your dad.
[ Mike laughs ]
SERVO: You guys wanna hear
about my fruit fly experiment?
Oh, actually, they're called
Drosophila melanogaster.
CROW: I hate him.
SERVO: The anal gang.
One more game or...
[ Music playing ]
Okay, let's go.
CROW: Barney,
bring the van around.
SERVO:
Did everyone make a potty?
Good luck.
CROW: So, who's got the car?
SERVO: Yeah, it takes 11 minutes
if he goes 600 miles an hour.
CROW: Well, at least
the traffic is with him.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Almost there yet?
When are we gonna be there?
I'm hungry.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO:
Marv called everyone in town
and asked them to stay home.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: I have a test tomorrow,
what am I doing?
[ Music playing ]
It's almost 10:51.
CROW: Oh, we're missing Leno.
Relax, we'll make it.
SERVO: So, when does
the suspense part begin?
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: So, are your dads
bean-eating alcoholics, too?
CROW: Marvin should really be
in his car seat.
SERVO: Oh, no.
I've seen
this random car directing.
What is it?
Looks like an accident.
What do we do?
It's the only direct street
to the ferry.
We'll have to detour.
Hurry up.
MIKE: Oh, he is smart.
That hurry-up part
was pure genius.
CROW: You bet.
Oh, sure.
Let's just sit around the table
and not leave early.
Good one, Marv.
[ Tom makes noises ]
We're there.
SERVO: It's really important
that,
♪ Whatever you do ♪
♪ Don't pay the ferryman ♪
CROW: Oh, could you do
something about that?
-MIKE: Okay...
-There's another ferry
in two minutes.
SERVO:
♪ Don't even fix a price ♪
All we do is wait.
And pray.
SERVO: Yeah, I'm sure,
what, with wars and famine
God is really interested
in your heist.
♪ Until he gets
you to the other side ♪
MIKE: Okay, that's it.
That's it.
-Bye-bye.
-CROW: Woo-ho-ho.
-Yay.
-What time is it?
-It's 10:58.
-We'll never make it.
MIKE: It was
a little harsh but...
-We've got to.
-CROW: It had to be done.
Come on.
CROW: Hey, the other side looks
exactly like the other side.
[ Music playing ]
MIKE: So does
this heist count towards
his outcome-based education?
CROW: Hmm, yes.
Kill your lights.
CROW: No, they don't need them
now that it's the middle
of the afternoon.
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: Look at this one.
CROW: I hope they didn't miss
the film's climax.
MIKE: I brought
my baritone sax.
It's almost 11:04.
We may have missed them.
SERVO: Again, maybe we didn't.
Come on.
CROW:
Oh, it's a sleepover caper.
[ Giggles ]
CROW: What's with the Tom
and Jerry music?
We're never late,
especially tonight.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
MIKE: What do you wanna do?
Accident. Stupid accident.
Listen.
SERVO: I'm late for the Village
People auditions.
[ Knocks ]
-It's Johnson.
-Is that you, Biff?
-JOHNSON: Yeah.
-CROW: Biff Johnson,
security guard.
-Hmm?
-Sorry, I'm late, Pete.
There was an accident.
Have fun.
SERVO: Oh, he's hitting them
with a hotdog.
CROW: Hmm.
SERVO: All right.
♪ We hate you, comrade ♪
SERVO: Let's pose them
so that they're kissing.
[ Servo and Crow laughs ]
[ Music playing ]
SERVO: ♪ Maryanne ♪
♪ Madame Light, Maryanne ♪
CROW: Ironically, Marv was about
to get a million dollar raise.
SERVO: Bet you'd be
pretty impressed,
if you knew
the shipping clerk here.
Why, I'm him.
[ Laughs ]
[ Tom makes noise ]
SERVO:
Damn, we need a locksmith.
Broke off.
Part of it's still in the lock.
Come on, it's 7 after,
we haven't got much time.
This might do it.
CROW: It wasn't even locked.
SERVO: Sure increased
the tension, though, huh?
MIKE: Guys,
we shouldn't be in here,
the sign said private.
CROW: A safe?
I thought you said the money
was in a toaster.
Well, you're in luck.
This one's easy.
It's 11:08.
Fingers crossed.
[ Knocks on door ]
-MRS. FISHER: Mr. Grant.
-SERVO: It's me, Mary.
MRS. FISHER: Are you there?
SERVO: I'm wearing my apron
and nothing else.
CROW: You're not eating beans
in there, are you?
It's Mrs. Fisher.
SERVO: I brought
my assortment of nuts.
CROW: This should be...
[ Music playing ]
[ Mrs. Fisher screams]
SERVO: Oh, my God.
He's a puppeteer.
CROW: Oh, how horrible.
MIKE: Many horses far away.
-SERVO: Ooh.
-CROW: Well, Vince
has assembled his brain trust.
[ Tom laughs ]
MIKE: I have no idea
what I'm doing.
CROW: Go home, go home.
MIKE: I have determined
it's a safe.
CROW: Park in the old canning
lot. What were you thinking?
-MIKE: Geez.
-CROW: Now turn your head
and cough.
SERVO: I have a girlfriend.
Oh.
MIKE: Guys, I think I'm coming
down with something.
[ Distant sirens wailing ]
CROW: Should I have not
called the cops?
MIKE: Should I tell them or not?
[ Crow laughs ]
Got it.
[ Music playing ]
-CROW: Oh.
-HARRY: Look at it.
-SERVO: Ooh.
-HARRY: Million bucks.
It's beautiful.
Come on.
We haven't much time.
SERVO: It's all Wisconsin Dells
Wampum Bucks.
What is he stealing?
SERVO: Take it easy, or I won't
have room for my sweater.
[ Laughs ]
CROW: Glad you can make
the heist, Mr. Disney.
SERVO: You shut up.
CROW: Got a hernia.
[ Music playing ]
Come on.
SERVO: I wanna show you my desk
before we leave.
SAM: Come on, Harry.
SERVO: Huh?
MIKE: Did I tell you we have
honor system candy here?
SERVO: Oh, ho, ho.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho.
CROW: Remember when I told you
about that guy
who doesn't pay for coffee?
Well, that's his desk
over there.
[ Tom laughs ]
MIKE: Unfortunately,
Marv will get caught
when he turns in his timecard
with these hours on it.
SERVO: Oops.
CROW: All of this because
of a strict English teacher.
[ Tom laughs ]
MARV: Okay.
That's far enough.
-SERVO: Oh, hi, Vince.
-Vince.
Give me that case
right now.
Vince, look, the cops
will be here any minute.
You can have some.
Shut up and give me
that money!
MIKE:
I'll write your paper, Vince.
[ Music playing ]
CROW: Damn, I missed Marv.
Are you crazy, Vince?
You didn't have to do that.
Come on, let's go, Larry.
SERVO: There goes the town's
only liquor store.
He's the last
of the great gentlemen.
MIKE: That's who we should've
gotten for the heist.
CROW: And seconds
into Vince's plan
-and it all goes wrong.
-...even have a gun.
-Vince.
-SERVO: And I helped.
Vince, come on.
Don't just stand there.
-You made me kill him.
-Come on.
Come on!
-Vince.
-SERVO: This is cashmere.
No, Vince.
SERVO:
Pepperidge Farm remembers...
[ Gunshots ]
CROW: I think this is about
more than the heist.
MIKE: Oh, geez.
There they are.
[ Gunshot ]
CROW: Hey, Baryshnikov!
Huh, liquid assets.
Million bucks.
-SERVO: He's juicy.
-MAN: Forget the money.
Let's get out of here.
I am loaded down
with snow, remember?
[ Distant siren wailing ]
SERVO: Ah, Ricky.
Don't move.
Now you have the right
to remain silent.
[ Gunshot ]
-Right there.
-Anything you say can
and will be used against you.
MIKE: Oh, no need to launder
the money then.
CROW: Would you stop?
Why?
CROW: I got punched
right in the store. Oh.
Oh, forgive me, I'm sorry, Pop.
Forgive me, Pop.
SERVO: I could really go
for a pop.
[ Sirens wailing ]
SERVO: Reverse-angle cops.
Oh, how'd the heist go?
Oh, geez, what a mess.
I just came from a scene
where some unemployed bean-eater
was swinging from the ceiling.
[ Mike imitates music ]
CROW: Should we just leave
the dead guys there?
SERVO: The crows will get them.
CROW: Yeah.
MIKE: Gross.
[ Servo makes noises ]
CROW: This is the PTA,
reminding you
to always do your homework.
SERVO: You know, in light
of this, cheating on a paper
wasn't that big a deal.
Coming up next on Nick at Nite.
One of the original
black and white
I Dream of Jeannie episodes.
Then F-Troop,
next on Nick at Nite.
CROW:
Filmed before a live audience.
MIKE: This has been
a Filmways presentation,
darling.
[ Tom and Crow humming ]
[ Doors closing ]
Boy, that was
a rugged movie, huh, guys?
Guys?
Oh, well.
I got a letter to read here.
It's from Donna Brinkhedder,
and put it on still store,
Cambot, if you would.
She writes, "Dear Mike,
Tom, Crow, and Gypsy.
"We've been watching your show
for some time
"and enjoyed it very much.
"But I'm afraid my husband
may be headed for trouble.
"Keith is a good,
kind, decent man,
but I think the dessert
has started to melt his..."
Ah-ha. All right.
Hand over the letter, Mike.
Don't move, give me the letter.
-Drop it. Drop it.
-No. No.
-Drop it.
-No. No. No. No.
Must continue to read letter,
Ann Landers told me to.
Sandwiches anyone?
Hmm?
You made me do this.
-Huh?
-You, woman, you.
[ Gypsy screaming,
Crow laughing ]
Oh, sorry. All right.
Don't move, I don't think
you wanna be doing that.
Just drop the gun
and nobody gets wet.
Oh, my God.
I'm a goner.
I'm wet.
You shot my boyfriend,
you dirty fuzz.
I ain't dead yet, cop.
Oh, I'm dead.
Oh, very nice.
Natural-born squirters.
at least you don't have a thing
trying to-- let go.
[ Forrester panting ]
There.
Here boy, where are you?
Here, boy. Here, boy.
Where are you?
Here-- hey.
Clay, have you seen
my dinosaur anywhere?
Oh, Frank, could this be
your dinosaur?
Oh, yeah. Thanks a lot.
That's-- oh. Oh.
Oh, ho, ho. Ho, ho.
Oh, ho. That hurt.
Oh, ho, ho. Aha, ho, ho.
That is skin there.
Ow, ow, ow.
[ Dinosaur makes noises ]
FRANK: Oh. Ah, ha, ha.
FRANK:
That's a sensitive spot there.
Yi, yi, yi.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, wow.
Wow.
Ho, ho, ho.
Oh, ho.
I must admit that stings.
Oh.
Ouchy, ouchy.
Bambi, oh, oh.
Yo, ho, ho.
Ah-ha-ha.
Wow.
Oh, ha, ha, ha, ho, ha, ha.
Oh, that stings.
Ouch, ouch.
Woo.
[ Dinosaur makes noises ]
[ Frank snorts]
[ Frank screams ]
Oh, that hurts.
Ouch.
[ Music playing ]
Million bucks.